<resources>
    <string name="app_name">L3</string>
    <string name="moscow">Moscow</string>
    <string name="st_petersburg">St. Petersburg</string>
    <string name="sochi">Sochi</string>
    <string name="vladivostok">Vladivostok</string>
    <string name="kazan">Kazan</string>
    <string name="moscowText">Moscow (pronunciation (info)) - the capital of Russia, the city of federal significance, the administrative center of the Central Federal District and the center of the Moscow region, which does not include [5]. The largest city in Russia and its subject is 12 615 279[2] people. (2019), the most populous of the cities fully located in Europe, is among the world`s top ten cities in terms of population[6], the largest Russian-speaking city in the world. The center of the Moscow urban agglomeration. The center of the Russian Orthodox Church. Historical capital of Grand Duchy of Moscow, Russian Empire, Russian Empire (in 1728-1730), Soviet Russia and USSR. Hero-City. Moscow is home to federal government bodies of the Russian Federation (with the exception of the Constitutional Court), embassies of foreign states, and the headquarters of the majority of the largest Russian commercial organizations and public associations. It is located in the west of Russia, on the Moscow River in the center of the East European Plain, in the interfluve of the Oka and Volga rivers. As a constituent entity of the Federation, Moscow borders on the Moscow and Kaluga regions. Moscow is the most popular tourist center in Russia. The Kremlin, Red Square, Novodevichy Monastery and Ascension Church in Kolomenskoye are on the UNESCO World Heritage List[7]. It is the most important transport hub: the city is served by 6 airports, 9 railway stations, 3 river ports (there is a river connection with the seas of the Atlantic and Arctic Ocean basins). Since 1935, the subway has been operating in Moscow. Moscow is the sports center of the country. In 1980, the XXII Summer Olympic Games were held in Moscow, and in 2018 the city became one of the hosts of the World Cup.</string>
    <string name="st_petersburgText">St. Petersburg (from 18 [31] August 1914 to 26 January 1924 [7] - Petrograd, from 26 January 1924 to 6 September 1991 [3] - Leningrad) - the second largest city in Russia[8]. The city of federal importance. Administrative center of the North-Western Federal District and Leningrad Region. It was founded on May 16 (27), 1703 by Peter I. In 1712-1918 it was the capital of the Russian state[9].  It was named in honor of St. Peter, the heavenly patron saint of the founding tsar, but over time it became more and more associated with the name of Peter I. The city is historically and culturally connected with a birth of the Russian Empire and occurrence of Russia in a modern history in a role of the European great power [10].  It is located in the northwest of the country, on the coast of the Gulf of Finland and at the mouth of the Neva River. In St. Petersburg there are the Constitutional Court of the Russian Federation, the Heraldic Council under the President of the Russian Federation, the authorities of the Leningrad region[11], the Interparliamentary Assembly of the CIS. The main command of the Navy and the headquarters of the Western Military District of the Armed Forces of Russia are also placed[12].  It was the center of three revolutions: 1905-1907, February and October revolutions of 1917[13]. During the Great Patriotic War in 1941-1944 872 days was in blockade, as a result of which about one million people died. On May 1, 1945, Leningrad was declared a heroic city. As of 2018, the federal city of St. Petersburg also includes three cities of military glory: Kronstadt, Kolpino, and Lomonosov.  Population: 5,383,890[4] (2019) people. St. Petersburg is the world`s northernmost city with a population of more than one million people. St. Petersburg is also the westernmost city with a population of over one million people in Russia. Among the cities fully located in Europe, it is the third largest city in terms of population, as well as the first in terms of population, which is not the capital city[14]. The innovative scenario of the "St. Petersburg Development Strategy to 2030" assumes that by 2030 the population will be 5.9 million[15]. The city is the center of St. Petersburg`s urban agglomeration. The area of the city is 1439[16] km², after the expansion of Moscow on July 1, 2012, St. Petersburg is the second largest city in the country.  St. Petersburg is an important economic, scientific and cultural centre of Russia, a major transport hub. The historic centre of the city and its associated monument complexes are included in the UNESCO World Heritage List[17]; it is one of the most important tourism centres in the country. Among the most significant cultural and tourist sites are the Hermitage, the Kunstkammer, the Mariinsky Theatre, the Russian National Library, the Russian Museum, the Peter and Paul Fortress, St. Isaac`s Cathedral[18] and Nevsky Prospekt. Among other things, the program of preservation and development of the historical center of St. Petersburg is aimed at preservation of cultural heritage objects. In 2018, about 8.5 million tourists visited St. Petersburg[19].</string>
    <string name="sochiText">Sochi is a city in Russia, located on the north-eastern coast of the Black Sea (the Russian Black Sea coast) in the Krasnodar region, at a distance of 1620 km from Moscow. The administrative center of the municipality is the resort city of Sochi.  Sochi is Russia`s largest resort city[9], an important transport hub[10][11][12][13], as well as a major economic and cultural center of the Russian Black Sea coast[14][15].  Unofficially it is also called the summer, southern and resort "capital" of Russia. In 2012 Forbes magazine recognized Sochi as the best city for doing business in the country[16].  Sochi is the longest city in Russia[17][unauthorized source?][18][unauthorized source?  In 2007 Sochi was elected the capital of the XXII Winter Olympic Games. On September 15, 2009 Sochi joined the World Union of Olympic Cities[19]. During the period of preparation for the Olympics, 500 billion rubles were spent on the development of the city and its infrastructure[20].  In 2018, the city hosted matches of the FIFA World Cup.</string>
    <string name="vladivostokText">Vladivostok is a city and port in the Far East of Russia; political, cultural, scientific, educational and economic center of the region; administrative center of Primorsky Krai and Vladivostok city district[3]. It is located on the Muravyov-Amursky Peninsula and islands in the Peter the Great Gulf of Japan.  The end point of the Trans-Siberian Railway. One of the largest seaports in the Far Eastern basin. The main base of the Pacific Fleet. The largest scientific and educational center of the Far Eastern region, including the Far Eastern Federal University and the Far Eastern Branch of the Russian Academy of Sciences.  It was founded as a military post "Vladivostok" in 1860 and received the status of a city in 1880. Since 1888 it has been the administrative center of the Primorsky Region, since 1938 - the Primorsky Territory.  Since October 12, 2015, it has been a free port (a port zone that enjoys special regimes of customs, tax, investment and related regulation).  Since December 13, 2018 - the center of the Far Eastern Federal District[4].  Population - 604,901 people. (2019).[⇨]</string>
    <string name="kazanText">Kazan (Tat. Kazan) - a city in Russia, the capital of the Republic of Tatarstan, a major port on the left bank of the Volga River at the confluence of the Kazanka River[6]. One of the largest economic, scientific, educational, religious, cultural and sports centers of Russia. The Kazan Kremlin is a UNESCO World Heritage Site.  Historically, the capital (center) of the Kazan khanate, Kazan kingdom, Kazan province and Tatar ASSR.  The city has a registered brand "The Third Capital of Russia"[7].  In 2005, the millennium of Kazan was celebrated.  Kazan has repeatedly hosted high-profile international competitions in various sports, including the 27th Summer Universiade in 2013, as well as a number of matches of the 2018 FIFA World Cup.  In 2014, TripAdvisor ranked the capital of Tatarstan 8th in the world and 3rd in Europe as the fastest growing tourist destination[8][9].  From 2017 to 2018, Kazan was ranked No. 3 in the Airbnb Russia`s most popular tourist destinations[10].  The city district borders on the Zelenodolsk, Vysokogorsk, Pestrechinsk and Laishevsk districts, and on the water area of the Kuibyshev reservoir - on the Verkhneuslonsk district.</string>
    <string name="forecastText"> temperature description</string>
    <string name="humidity">Humidity</string>
    <string name="cloudiness">Cloudiness</string>
</resources>
